Kheel, Theodore W. Books and Articles 6021/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Notes: Authors include: Robert M. Solow; Milton Friedman; Gardner Ackley; John T. Dunlop; Arthur M. Ross; E. H. Phelps Brown; Harry B. Johnson; Allan H. Meltzer; Philip B. Kurland; Frederick R. Livingston; Theodore W. Schultz; Douglass V. Brown; Robben W. Fleming; George J. Stigler; Benjamin Aaron; Ralph Helstein
- Has the Leopard Changed Its Spots?, 1971; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Has the Leopard Changed Its Spots?, 1971; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A Hemispheric Venture, 2000; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Hemispheric Venture: Thirty-Five Years of Culture at the Americas Society, 2000; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: Americas Society
    Language: English and Spanish.
- A History of the Port of New York Authority, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A History of the Port of New York Authority, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Author: Daniel Goldberg
- How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes: Labor Report Bulletin no.7 (1963:Aug. 15)
  - Item 2: How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes: Labor Report Bulletin no.7 (1963:Aug. 15). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes: Galleys for Labor Report Bulletin no.7 (1963:Aug. 15)
- How the Establishment Got Theirs, 1972; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: How the Establishment Got Theirs: The Defeat of the Transportation Bond Issue, 1972; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Author: Fred Powledge
    Notes: Published in New York, v.5:no.1 (1972:Jan. 3)
- How to Handle Problems of Integrating Your Workforce, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How to Handle Problems of Integrating Your Workforce, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Notes: Prentice-Hall Executive Report on Business Information, Section 3 (1964:Nov. 14)
  - Item 2: How to Handle Problems of Integrating Your Workforce, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Notes: Prentice-Hall Executive Report on Business Information, Section 3 (1964:Nov. 14). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: How to Handle Problems of Integrating Your Workforce, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Notes: Prentice-Hall Executive Report on Business Information, Section 3 (1964:Nov. 14). Copy 3.
- How to Prevent Strikes by Public Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: How to Prevent Strikes by Public Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-First Annual Conference on Labor
  - Item 2: How to Prevent Strikes by Public Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-First Annual Conference on Labor. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: How to Prevent Strikes by Public Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-First Annual Conference on Labor. Copy 3.
- How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22)
  - Item 2: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Uncorrected draft of article published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22)
  - Item 5: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Uncorrected draft of article published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22). Copy 2
  - Item 6: How to Stop Cars From Crushing the City, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Notes: Uncorrected draft of article published in New York, v.2:no.38 (1969:Sep. 22). Copy 3
- Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Author: United Nations Development Programme
    Notes: Canada Displaces Japan at the Top of the Human Development Index
  - Item 2: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Foreign Aid: A Small Pie with a Fat Slice for Arms Buyers and a Mere Sliver for Poor People
  - Item 3: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Global Markets Put World's Poorest at $500 Billion Disadvantage
  - Item 4: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Global Poverty and Global Pollution Are Linked
  - Item 5: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Growing Gap In World Incomes: Richest Billion People are 150 Times Wealthier Than the Poorest Billion
  - Item 6: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Human Development: A Blueprint for Action
  - Item 7: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: UNDP Report Calls for a Summit on Human Development and Sweeping Reform of World Bank, IMF and GATT, Creation of UN "Development Security Council" as Ways of Narrowing Gap Between Rich and Poor.
  - Item 8: Human Development Report, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Notes: Unrestricted Labour Migration Would Earn Developing Countries Hundreds of Billions of Dollars
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Author: John R. Moroney; Bruce T. Allen; John E. Drotning; David B. Lipsky; John F. Burton, Jr.; John E. Parker; Stuart O. Schweitzer; Orwell de R. Foenander; Robert J. Carlsson; James W. Robinson; P. D. Shrimali; Peter S. Barth; Walter Galenson
    Notes: v.22:no.2 (1969:Jan.)
  - Item 2: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Author: Arnold R. Weber; Carmelo Mesa-Lago; Robert Raimon; Vladimir Stoikov; Alice H. Cook; John S. Hirsch, Jr.; William A. Howard; Lester O. Bumas; Bruno Stein; Arthur Carol; Samuel Parry
    Notes: v.22:no.3 (1969:Apr.)
  - Item 3: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Author: Charles Craypo; Daniel J. B. Mitchell; Jean T. McKelvey; Robert Kilroy-Silk; Malcolm H. Liggett; Ronald S. Koot; David F. Bramhall; Herrington J. Bryce; John M. Glasgow; Arthur Carol; Samuel Parry; Shelley Akabas
    Notes: v.22:no.4 (1969:July)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Author: David B. Ross; Stephan Michelson; Richard L. Rowan; Harrsion M. Trice; James Belasco; Joseph A. Alutto; Andrew C. Gross; Damodar N. Gujarati; John Pencavel; John F. Burton, Jr.; Robert J. Carlsson; James W. Robinson
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1969:Oct.)
  - Item 2: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1970; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Author: Byron Yaffe; Roger L. Bowlby; William R. Schriver; John P. Windmuller; Howard G. Foster; R. A. Hudson Rosen; James E. Jonish; David J. Smyth; Peter D. Lowe
    Notes: v.23:no.4 (1970:July)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Author: John P. Windmuller; Lewis Minkin; Richard J. Willey; Nils Elvander; Penny Gill Martin; Joseph R. Grodin; James L. Stern; Kenneth A. Root; Stephan M. Hills; Richard M. Scheffler; George Iden
    Notes: v.26:no.2 (1973:Jan.)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Notes: v.28:no.1 (1974:Oct.)
- Industrial Relations Research Associatin 14th Annual Meeting, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 14th Annual Meeting, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Industrial Relations Research Association
- Industrial Relations Research Associatin 15th Annual Meeting, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 15th Annual Meeting, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Industrial Relations Research Associatin 22nd Annual Meeting, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 22nd Annual Meeting, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Industrial Relations Research Associatin 23rd Annual Meeting, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 23rd Annual Meeting, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Industrial Relations Research Associatin 24th Annual Meeting, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 24th Annual Meeting, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Research Associatin 24th Annual Meeting, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Innovations: Scientific, Technological, and Social, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Innovations: Scientific, Technological, and Social, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Author: Dennis Gabor
- An Insiders Guide to the UN, 2004; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: An Insiders Guide to the UN, 2004; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Author: Linda Fasulo
- International Agreements Are Not Well Monitored, 1992; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International Agreements Are Not Well Monitored, 1992; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Government Accounting Office
- Interplay, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Interplay, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Interplay
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1969:Aug./Sep.)
  - Item 2: Interplay, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1969:Oct.)
  - Item 3: Interplay, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1969:Nov.)
  - Item 4: Interplay, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1969/1970:Dec./Jan.)
- Interracial Housing, 1951; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Interracial Housing: A Psychological Evaluation of a Social Experiment, 1951; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Author: Morton Deutsch; Mary Evans Collins
- An Introduction to Complementary and Integrative Medicine, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: An Introduction to Complementary and Integrative Medicine, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Author: Weill Medical College of Cornell University
  - Item 2: An Introduction to Complementary and Integrative Medicine, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: An Introduction to Complementary and Integrative Medicine, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Is a Negotiated Peace Possible?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Is a Negotiated Peace Possible?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: Published in Interplay, v.3:no.14 (1970:Nov.). Also includes Kheel's op-ed, "An Issue on Conflict"
  - Item 2: Is a Negotiated Peace Possible?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: Published in Interplay, v.3:no.14 (1970:Nov.). Also includes Kheel's op-ed, "An Issue on Conflict". Copy 2. Photocopy
  - Item 3: Is a Negotiated Peace Possible?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: Published in Interplay, v.3:no.14 (1970:Nov.). Also includes Kheel's op-ed, "An Issue on Conflict". Copy 3. Photocopy
- Is Imitation the Sincerest Form of Flattery?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Is Imitation the Sincerest Form of Flattery?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: No author listed: believed to be Theodore W. Kheel
  - Item 2: Is Imitation the Sincerest Form of Flattery?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: No author listed: believed to be Theodore W. Kheel. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Is Imitation the Sincerest Form of Flattery?, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: No author listed: believed to be Theodore W. Kheel. Copy 3.
- Is the Strike Outmoded?, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Is the Strike Outmoded?, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Is the Strike Outmoded?, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Is the Strike Outmoded?, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Is the Strike Outmoded?, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: Paper delivered at Fifth Annual Collective Bargaining Forum, June 7, 1973.
- It Seems Like Yesterday, 1989; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: It Seems Like Yesterday: A Photographic Album of Old-Time Easton and Phillipsburg, 1989; Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: Ronald W. Wynkoop, Sr.
- A Job for Mr. Mitchell, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Job for Mr. Mitchell, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Author: The Nation
    Notes: Published in The Nation, August 2, 1971.
- Jobs for the Hard-To-Employ, 1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Jobs for the Hard-To-Employ: New Directions For a Public-Private Partnership, 1978; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Author: Research and Policy Committee
    Notes: January 1978.
- The Key to Labor-Management Peace and Prosperity in New York State, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Key to Labor-Management Peace and Prosperity in New York State, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Author: Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Relations
    Notes: Legislative Document (1966) no.40: Report of the New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Relations For the Year 1965-1966.
- The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Author: Rutgers University
    Notes: Program for reception and book signing.
  - Item 5: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Notes: Program for reception and book signing. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Notes: Program for reception and book signing. Copy 3.
  - Item 7: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Author: Four Walls Eight Windows
    Notes: Postcard announcing publication.
  - Item 8: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Notes: Postcard announcing publication. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: The Keys to Conflict Resolution, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Notes: Postcard announcing publication. Copy 3.
- Kheel on Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Kheel on Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Author: John Herling's Labor Letter
    Notes: Published in John Herling's Labor Letter, December 14, 1968.
  - Item 2: Kheel on Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Notes: Published in John Herling's Labor Letter, December 14, 1968. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Kheel on Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Notes: Published in John Herling's Labor Letter, December 14, 1968. Copy 3.
- Lawren Stewart Harris: A Painter's Progress, 2000; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Lawren Stewart Harris: A Painter's Progress, 2000; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: Andrew Hunter
- Labor-Management Relations in Industrial Society, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations in Industrial Society, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Notes: Published in The Search for Identity: Essays on the American Character.
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Relations in Industrial Society, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Notes: Published in The Search for Identity: Essays on the American Character. Copy 2.
- Labour's Visionary: Lord Hirshfield, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Labour's Visionary: Lord Hirshfield, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Author: Godfrey Gideon
  - Item 2: Labour's Visionary: Lord Hirshfield, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Labour's Visionary: Lord Hirshfield, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Lindsay ant the "Power Brokers", 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Lindsay ant the "Power Brokers", 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Author: Peter Maas
    Notes: Published in New York, v.1:no.38 (1968:Dec. 23), "The City Politic" section
  - Item 2: Lindsay ant the "Power Brokers", 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Notes: Published in New York, v.1:no.38 (1968:Dec. 23), "The City Politic" section. Copy 2.
- Lithopinion, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Lithopinion, 1966; Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Author: Robert C. Weaver; Charles Abrams; Donald Shaughnessy; Dick Netzer; Stephen R. Currier; David B. carlson; Louis Winnick; John E. Ullmann; Herman D. Goldberg; Francine Grace; Sam Zagoria; Fredric D. Appel; John George Kauper
    Notes: Issue on "Making Our Cities Workable"
- The Making of Presidents, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Kheel: The Artist as Optimist, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Author: Newsweek
    Notes: Published in Newsweek, July 12, 1965. Photocopy.
- Man and Superman, 1960; Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Man and Superman, 1960; Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Author: Bernard Shaw
- The Man They Call When the Strike Is On, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Man They Call When the Strike Is On, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Author: The Christian Science Monitor; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Interview with Theodore Kheel published in The Christian Science Monitor, September 22, 1967.
  - Item 2: The Man They Call When the Strike Is On, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Notes: Interview with Theodore Kheel published in The Christian Science Monitor, September 22, 1967. Copy 2.
- ManMade Planet, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ManMade Planet: Photographs by Wolfgang Volz, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Author: Bernard Mensch; Peter Pachnicke; Christo and Jean-Claude; Manfred Schneckenburger; Werner Spise
  - Item 2: ManMade Planet: Photographs by Wolfgang Volz, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: ManMade Planet: Photographs by Wolfgang Volz, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Manager's Guide to Resolving Legal Disputes, 1985; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Manager's Guide to Resolving Legal Disputes: Better Results Without Litigation, 1985; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: James F. Henry; Jethro K. Lieberman
- Managing Change, 1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Managing Change: Advance Agenda, 1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board
    Notes: January 19-20, 1967.
  - Item 2: Managing Change: Advance Agenda, 1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 19-20, 1967. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Managing Change: Advance Agenda, 1967; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: January 19-20, 1967. Copy 3.
- Martindale-Hubbell Law Directory, 1977; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Martindale-Hubbell Law Directory, 1977; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Author: Martindale- Hubbell
    Notes: Vol. 4: Lawyers: New York City-Pennsylvania
- The Master Locksmith of Deadlock Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Master Locksmith of Deadlock Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Notes: Published in Business Week, no.2010 (1968:Mar.)
- Measuring Benefits of Government Investments, 1965; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Measuring Benefits of Government Investments, 1965; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Author: Robert Dorfman; Frederic M. Scherer; Ruth P. Mack; Sumner Myers; Burton A. Weisbrod; Gary Fromm; Herbert Mohring; Jerome Rothenberg; Herbert E. Klarman
    Notes: Papers presented at a conference of experts, November 7-9, 1963.
- Mediator, 1970; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Mediator, 1970; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Author: Fred C. Shapiro
    Notes: Profile Theodore Kheel in New Yorker, August 1, 1970.
- Mediator's Deskbook, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Mediator's Deskbook, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Author: Kathleen M. Scanlon
- Memorandum on the Formalization and Finance of a Sound Transportation Program for the New York Metropolitan Region, 1971; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Memorandum on the Formalization and Finance of a Sound Transportation Program for the New York Metropolitan Region, 1971; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 9, 1971.
- Metropolitan Transportation Politics and the New York Region, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Metropolitan Transportation Politics and the New York Region, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Author: Jameson W. Doig
    Notes: Number six: Metropolitan Politics Series
- A Mind At a Time, 2002; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Mind At a Time, 2002; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: Mel Levine
- Minutes of the Proceedings of a Meeting of the Temporary State Charter Revision Commission, 1972; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Proceedings of a Meeting of the Temporary State Charter Revision Commission, 1972; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Author: State Charter Revision Commission
    Notes: October 30, 1972.
- Model Rules of Professional Conduct, 1992; Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Model Rules of Professional Conduct, 1992; Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Author: Center for Professional Responsibility
- Mollie and Other War Pieces, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Mollie and Other War Pieces, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Author: A. J. Liebling
- More Than a Stalemate, 1970; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: More Than a Stalemate, 1970; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: Op-ed in Interplay, v.3:no.15 (1970:Dec.)
- Motions During Trial, 1960; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Motions During Trial, 1960; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Author: Howard Hilton Spellman
- Multiple Choice/Careers For the Future, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Multiple Choice/Careers For the Future, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Author: Stanley H. Ruttenberg
  - Item 2: Multiple Choice/Careers For the Future, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Multiple Choice/Careers For the Future, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The Myth of Lazyness, 2003; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Myth of Lazyness, 2003; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- NLRB General Counsel, 1980; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: NLRB General Counsel: Unreviewable Power to Refuew to Issue an Unfair Labor Practice Complaint, 1980; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Author: Michael C. McClintok
- Nafanua, 1997; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Nafanua: Saving the Samoan Rain Forest, 1997; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Author: Paul Alan Cox; Michael Rothman